const myQuestions = [
    {
      question: 'I ____ to being spoken to like that!',
      answers: {
        a: 'don\'t get used',
        b: 'used',
        c: 'am not used',
        d: 'use'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'I find it hard ____ to the dark evenings in winter.',
      answers: {
        a: 'don\'t get used',
        b: 'used',
        c: 'to getting',
        d: 'to get used'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'I haven\'t studied for ages and I\'m finding it hard to get used to ____ every day.',
      answers: {
        a: 'study',
        b: 'studying',
        c: 'studied',
        d: 'being studied'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'You\'ll have to get used to ____ on the right when you live there.',
      answers:  {
        a: 'drove',
        b : 'driven',
        c : 'drive',
        d : 'driving'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'd'
  },
  {
      question: 'I found it hard to get used  to ____ in such a hot country.',
      answers: {
        a: 'live',
        b: 'living',
        c: 'lived', 
        d: 'life'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'b' 
  },
  {
      question: 'Which sentence is NOT correct?',
      answers: {
        a: 'My grandmother would have long, fair hair.',
        b: 'We would go swimming every Friday',
        c: 'There would be a park here.', 
        d: 'We would go to the zoo every summer.'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'a'
  },
  {
      question: 'I\'m not used to ____ so much tea.',
      answers:  {
        a: 'drinking',
        b: 'drink',
        c: 'drunk', 
        d: 'get'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'a'
  },
  {
      question: 'I ____ like football then but I like it now',
      answers: {
        a: 'didn\'t used to',
        b: 'wouldn\'t',
        c: 'didn\'t use to', 
        d: 'wouldn\'t to'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'c'
  },
  {
      question: 'You can use "would" to talk about...',
      answers:  {
        a: 'past states',
        b: 'past habits (actions)',
        c: 'past habits(actions) and past states', 
        d: 'events in the past'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'b'
  },
  {
      question: 'You can use "used to" to talk about...(you can choose two or more options)',
      answers: {
        a: 'past habits (actions)',
        b: 'past states',
        c: 'events in the past', 
        d: 'use of objects'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'b'
  }
  ];
